WILSEN JULIUS

Jakarta Barat • 085355228808 • wilsenbinus@gmail.com https://github.com/Williuss

SUMMARY

I am a fifth semester undergraduate student of Computer Science major in BINUS University and i am currently taking intelligence system streaming. I'm passionate about Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning & Big Data Processing. With my desire to learn something new, i aim to enhance my skills and gain valuable experience from my surroundings.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Part Time Al Teaching Assistant, Binus Center Bintaro Sokrates September 2024 - Present

• I serve as a part-time teaching assistant for an Al-driven curriculum, where I support the lead instructor in enhancing the clarity and accessibility of the material. My role involves ensuring that the content is effectively communicated to the participants, primarily companies & instance looking to transition towards digital transformation.

Math Tutor Volunteer, Teach for Indonesia

May 2024 - June 2024

- Conducted teaching sessions for students from 1st grade to 3rd grade in mathematics.
- Developing a compact and appropriate curriculum for elementary school students.
- Collaborating with fellow teaching team members to deliver organized and effective teaching sessions.

Data Administrator Intern, PT. Central Warisan Indah Makmur

June 2022 - August 2022

- Boosted team efficiency which resulted to a faster monthly financial report.
- Streamlined project workflows, enhancing overall efficiency by 25%.
- Led a team in successfully delivering a complex engineering project on time and within allocated budget.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science | GPA: 3.52

Sep 2022 - Present

Bina Nusantara University

- Streaming in Intelligence System.
- Activist of Himpunan Teknik Informatika BINUS 2023/2024 (Education Division)

Natural Science Major | Grade: 91.5

July 2019 - May 2022

Darma Yudha Senior High School

Learned about the living creature science and applied mathematics

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Machine Learning, AI, Web Development, UI/UX Design, Data Analytics
- Languages: Bahasa Indonesia, English
- Certifications: Machine Learning with Python, Python 101 for Data Science
- Non Technical Skills: Collaboration, Time Management, Problem Solving, Critical Thinking